deathby1000papercuts.com 2016-12-21

# Privacy Policy -

**Our Commitment to Privacy**  
Immediate Financial is committed to keeping private, within a secure environment, the data that we collect through the use of our software. We therefore aim to provide an environment in which you know that we respect your right to privacy and will do whatever we can to ensure that any information you provide to us remains private. Any such information will only be used for the purposes described below.

We have implemented policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorised access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorised modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. All our employees, who have access to and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data.

The Data Protection Act requires companies and individuals who process and retain information about their customers to tell the customer how the information will be used and to what purposes it will be put.

This Privacy Policy explains the steps we take to ensure information about you is kept secure and confidential. This Privacy Policy also explains what happens to the information that you supply to us. We will not use your personal data in any other way without first informing you.

**Please take time to read this Privacy Policy carefully as once you use our website you will be regarded as having read and accepted this Privacy Policy. You should not use our website if you do not accept this policy.**

The Data Controller is Immediate Financial (company number 5829935). Immediate Financial complies with the Data Protection Act, and is registered as a data controller with the Information Commissioner’s Office.

If you have any queries about this Privacy Policy or any requests concerning your personal information, please write to our address below.

Data Protection Officer   
Immediate Financial   
Huxley House  
Weyside Park  
Catteshall Lane  
Godalming  
GU7 1XE 

**Why we collect and use your personal information**  
Immediate Financial collect and use your personal details to allow us to provide the service which you are seeking, and to enable us to ensure that our services are as personalised and accurate as possible. Personal information is required for us to be able to generate accurate quotes for the products that you require.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
By using our website, and completing an enquiry form, you will be regarded as having given your consent to Immediate Financial contacting you by phone, e-mail or otherwise to inform you about products and services that may be of interest to you.

Immediate Financial's price comparison service involves us passing the details you input to our website to our partners. This enables the partners to provide us with quotations on the products and services that you have requested. If you do decide to enter into a contract with one of our partners then the information which we have supplied to them (as well as any further information requested by them to enable to them to complete the contract) will be held by the partner. You are therefore advised to read the partners privacy policy before entering into any contract with them.

We may also share your personal information with other and other professional advisers, financial organisations and advisers, sponsors and advertisers. Such parties may contact you by phone, e-mail or otherwise to inform you about products and services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer to opt out of such direct marketing activity, please let us know by any means convenient for you so that we may remove your personal data from our marketing database. However, please remember that by opting out, we will not be able to contact you about products or services that may benefit you.

If you provide us with information about another person, you confirm that they have appointed you to act for them and they have consented to the processing of their personal data as set out above.

If your enquiry is in regard to Mortgage advice, we will arrange for one of our to contact you by phone. In some circumstances, we may arrange for an alternative Mortgage Adviser to contact you. In these cases, we will notify you of the name of the adviser and request your permission for your details to be sent to them before any contact is made.

Immediate Financial may also disclose your personal information to governmental bodies and regulators where required to do so by law, or where necessary for Immediate Financial to fulfil our regulatory obligations.

**Information disclosure outside of the UK**  
It is possible that, by using our services, your data will be transferred to companies outside of the European Union, for example where the partners’ computer systems or calls centres are based abroad. Immediate Financial will only transfer your personal details outside of the European Union where the partner(s) have confirmed, via contractual agreement, that they will hold and use your personal data in line with European Union standards.

**Helping with your Insurance quotation**  
By submitting an insurance quotation through our website, you agree that the top 3 Insurance providers and/or brokerages in your search results may contact you by telephone for a limited time following the submission of your enquiry. This allows the insurance provider and/or brokerages to enquire as to whether you would like to proceed with the quotation, and also allows them, where applicable, to see if they are able to present you with any special offers, further discounts or incentives relating to the quotation you received.

**Call Monitoring**  
Phone calls to Immediate Financial may be recorded for training and monitoring purposes, in accordance with UK law.

**Credit Reference Searches**  
Please note that our Trusted Business Partners may make, or cause searches to be made, at a credit reference agency, or agencies. You should be aware that such searches will be shown in any other searches that are made in connection with credit applications made by yourself or other members of your household. The disclosure of multiple searches may adversely affect your credit profile and may make credit more difficult for you, or other members of your household, to obtain.

**Your rights to your personal information**  
You have the right to know what personal information we hold about you and to whom it has been disclosed.

Please write to the address above, confirming that you are making a request for your personal information under the Data Protection Act, and enclosing a fee of £10 made payable to Immediate Financial. We are entitled to charge you this fee under the Data Protection Act to cover our administration costs. 

Immediate Financial aims to comply with requests for access to personal information as quickly as possible, but within 40 days.

If any information we hold is inaccurate, we will make the necessary amendments and confirm to you have that these have been made.

**Tracking Data Policy**  
We obtain data by using cookies or JavaScript files. These files help us analyse web traffic and lets us know when you visit a particular web page. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes.

Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. We know that people have concerns about cookies, but we believe that the benefit we both gain from their proper use is worthwhile. You may set your web browser (Microsoft Internet Explorer or Netscape Navigator) to notify you of cookie placement requests or decline cookies completely.

**Changes to the Policy**  
We may need to amend the Privacy Policy from time to time. Any such amendment will take effect as soon as it is posted on the website. You are therefore encouraged to familiarise yourself with the Privacy Policy on a regular basis. 

View our Terms & Conditions to view our terms and conditions.

## We can solve any debt problem

Debt can be stifling, there’s no arguing with that. But we can help.

Whatever you debt problems, however deep in the red you find yourself, we can help you find a way out, but you’ve got to act fast to stop it growing out of control.

Whether you’re after an IVA, a Debt Management Plan, or simply some advice tailored to your specific situation, get in touch and let us see what we can do for you.

Find out if you qualify
